# JEAN MAVERICK BOEZEM

Leeuwarden Eewal 72 A · 0657749614

#### InspironDell007@outlook.com

Hello to you friend lets start this personal bio with a small fact my name Maverick means Dare Devil. I'm a decently social person I like to work in teams and alone and I'm a dog lover. I have 4 years of working experience in a big company, so I've developed a good work ethic, team working skills and leader skills/experience (reference letter in the back). During my time at Price- smart I was best known for 2 qualities precision and creativity aka outside the box thinking I was always up for a challenge and I liked problem solving.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**APRIL 2014 - MAART 2015** 

### MEMBERSHIP/CUSTOMER SUPPORT CLERK, PRICESMART

While working in this department I learned for the first time how to deal with all kinds of people of all different nationalities and background being that Aruba is Tourist hot zone. I also learned how to handle my temper and how to work well under pressure, I also started learning the basics of team work and work discipline.

**MAART 2015 - DECEMBER 2015** 

## RECEIVING CLERK, PRICESMART

In this department I learned mostly what goes on in the back of a large warehouse and how to deal with external supplier companies. Before I got transferred to another department I was about to start official training of how to operate a forklift but before this I had already fiddled around with them. I did completely learn how to use a scissor lift.

JANUARI 2016 - AUGUSTUS 2017

## TECH CENTER CLERK, PRICESMART

Here I started learning how to become a team leader as I was the senior worker of this department with the most experience with technology I was put into the role of group leader of a group of 10. After 10 months as group leader my supervisor started teaching me the roles of supervisor in the hopes that I could take he's place so that he would be free to get promoted. During my time here, I also gained a lot of experience in team-work being that as group leader I would have to work/communicate with other departments all the time in trying to fill my supervisors shoes.

#### **EDUCATION**

**AUGUSTUS 2014 - JULI 2017** 

## HAVO DIPLOMA (N+T EN N+G), AVOND HAVO ORANJESTAD

**AUGUSTUS 2017 - JULI 2018** 

#### ELECTRICAL ENGINEER, NHL

During this year I learned to better my Dutch and adjust my way of studying.

**AUGUSTUS 2018 - ONGOING** 

#### **HBO ICT, NHL STENDEN**

In this course until now I have learned the basics of coding in 3 languages that are as follow: C#, HTML, CSS. Part of this course also is "Professional studies" which helps me get a professional attitude when it comes to dealing with people and clients.

**AUGUSTUS 2018 - ONGOING** 

### ETS TOEFL IBT, CURCACOU

This is a standard English test that scores my skill with English.

#### • SKILLS

- 4 out 5 Experience with working on Microsoft apps
- Basics of programming in C#, HTML, CSS
- 4 out of 5 Mastery over Dutch writing and
- 5 out of 5 Mastery over English writing and speech.
- 3 out of 5 Mastery over Spanish mostly speech but can still write.

# professional products

- ,
- •
- ,
- ,
- ,
- ,

## Reflections

- ,
- .
- ,
- .
- ,
- ,
- .